Two men with nothing in common... except the blood in their veins.
Harry & Son is a drama film directed by Paul Newman.
Widower Harry Keach is a construction worker who was raised to
appreciate the importance of working for a living.
He takes a dim view of his sensitive son Howard's lackadaisical lifestyle and has a strained
relationship with his daughter Nina as he does not approve of her husband.
When Harry is fired from his job, his life changes drastically as he
is made to focus on the relationships around him.
Harry Keach, played by Paul Newman.
Howard Keach, played by Robby Benson.
Katie Wilowski, played by Ellen Barkin.
Tom Keach, played by Wilford Brimley.
Sally, played by Judith Ivey.
Raymond, played by Ossie Davis.
Harry & Son is a 1984 American drama film directed
by Paul Newman, who also stars.
The screenplay by Newman and Ronald Buck focuses on the relationship between blue-collar worker Harry Keach
and his son Howard (Robby Benson), who fails at various odd jobs while aspiring to be a writer.
Joanne Woodward, Ellen Barkin, Ossie Davis, Wilford
Brimley, and Judith Ivey also star.
The film also features Morgan Freeman.
The film explores themes of pet shop, beer, writer, birth, widower.
The tone is emotional.